YYeTs人人影视字幕组出品
更多原创字幕翻译 请登陆www.YYeTs.net
■
时间轴：   YY
后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
■
翻译： 蔷爆  取子小Q  亚洲帅哥MT  YY
后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
■
校对： YY    后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
老爸老妈浪漫史
第六季  第六集
孩子们  在2010年的秋天
Kids, in the fall of 2010,
我们的朋友斯图尔特和克劳蒂娅的孩子降临人世
our friends Stuart and Claudia had a baby,
马修和莉莉立马就去拜访了
and Marshall and Lily were the first
这对兴奋的新父母
to visit the happy new parents.
你们给孩子取名字了吗
So, have you guys landed on a name yet?
我们在努力  可这比想像的难多了
We're trying, but it's tougher than you think.
我喜欢蒂芙妮
You see, I like "Tiffany."
我可不希望我女儿的名字跟妓女一样
And I don't want my daughter to have a whore's name.
那是我妈的名字
That's my mother's name.
我知道
I know.
我知道了
Oh, I got it.
那孩子以你来命名吧  "性冷淡泼妇"
How 'bout we name the baby after you-- "Frigid Shrew."
那还不错
Oh, that's good.
不  不  不
No, no, no, no.
叫她"伏特加"吧
Let's call her "Vodka."
至少嗜酒如命的你会抱紧她
Then at least we know you'd hold her tight
打死也不撒手
and never let her go!
不要拿伏特加说事儿  没它哪来的孩子
Don't knock the vodka. Wouldn't have a kid without it.
斯图尔特  你简直太
Stuart, you are so...
我们不会这样的  对不对
That's not gonna be us, right?
给孩子取个名字还能多难
I mean, how hard can it be to name a baby?
没错  看看这个孩子
Right? I mean, just look at her. Yeah.
她显然该叫
She's clearly a...
-埃米莉  -丽莎
- Emily.  - Lisa.
-丽莎  -埃米莉
- Lisa?!  - Emily?!
我列了个名单  里面的名字都超赞
Okay!  I made a list of awesome baby names.
从头开始  第一个是
Starting at the top: number one...
马修  我不得不打断你一下
I'm gonna stop you right here, Marshall.
你管一个胖乎乎白人小孩叫勒布朗
You name a chubby white kid "LeBron,"
结果他腰围比篮球筐还粗
and he's the one getting stuffed in the basketball hoop.
那我把这些篮球明星的都删了  沙奎尔
Then I'm also crossing off, um, "Shaquille"...
哈基姆  迪坎贝
"Hakeem," and "Dikembe."
罗伯怎么样
Hey, what about "Rob"?
罗伯
"Rob"?
-不  -为什么不
- No.  - Why not?
罗伯  你打算怎么做火鸡
Hey, Rob. What are you gonna make a turkey?
罗伯不行
Not "Rob."
瑞安怎么样
Okay, um, how about "Ryan"?
瑞安不行
Not "Ryan."
强尼
"Johnny?"
金鱼在哪去了
Hey, where's the goldfish?
强尼不行
Not "Johnny."
吉尔也不行
Or "Gil."
杰里米
"Jeremy."
杰里米  不要
Jeremy, no!
杰里米绝对不行
Definitely not "Jeremy."
他画的东西毫无创意可言
His stuff was so derivative.
天啊  莉莉
Well, I mean, geez, Lily.
不管你们取什么名字
Well, whatever you do,
都不会叫贝基对吧
do not name your baby "Becky," right?
-为什么  -什么
- Why?  - What? What?
贝基  我的新搭档
Becky. My new co-anchor?
你们从来没看过我的节目
Don't you guys ever watch the show?
-亲爱的  我试过  -我们的数字视频录像机
- Oh, honey, I really try.  - Our DVR won't recognize it
不能把它识别为电视节目
as a television program.
我看了
I watched.
罗宾坚持让我目睹一下  贝基有多么糟糕
Robin insisted I confirm how "awful" Becky is,
所以昨天晚上我确认了一下
so last night I checked it out.
这个地区的和谈
Peace talks in the region
被称为"卓有成效"
have been described as, "productive."
贝基
Becky?
昨天晚上  在斯塔腾岛
Last night, in Staten Island,
墨西哥卷饼商贩被持枪抢劫
a taco cart owner was robbed at gunpoint.
那太可怜了
That's so sad.
贝基  我们是新闻工作者
Becky, we're-we're journalists.
不能对这些新闻感情用事
We can't get emotional about the news, we...
不
Oh, no!
他们偷了他所有的钱
They stole all his money and then pelted him
还用卷饼里的肉打他
with his own taco meat!
谁会做这种事
Who would do that?
如果你看了这个故事  我们就会揭发出来
Well, if you read the story, we might find out.
我能报关于马的这个吗
Oh, can I do this one, about the horse?
马什么的  最有爱了
I love horseys.
马死了
Aww, the horse died.
大伙
Guys!
这些新闻全部都让人悲痛
This news is all really sad.
你就毫不留情地说吧  贝基怎么样
Okay, no holds barred-- what'd you think of Becky?
我觉得她非常迷人
I thought she was charming.
你也觉得
You, too?
有人能给我解释一下
Can somebody please explain to me
为什么这个小妞要在男人面前装童真
why the little girl act works on men?
你想要听长话长说  还是长话短说呢
You want the long version or the short version?
短说
Short version.
长话短说
谁是你爹地
Who's your daddy?
当这句话从你口中说出来
You know, when you think about that,
感觉特变态
that phrase is really creepy.
不  挺有意思的
No, it's not. It's fun.
来  我说一遍
Here, watch this.
莉莉  谁是你爹地
Hey, Lily... Who's your daddy?
好吧  我把中心思想说明白点
Okay, uh, let me get this straight.
在这个剧情里
So, in, uh, in this scenario,
因为你这么宠爱莉莉
because you make such sweet love to Lily,
现在她是你女儿
she is now your daughter.
不  她不是我女儿
No, she is not my daughter.
我只是她床上的主人
I'm just her daddy.
真让人厌恶
Wow. That is disgusting.
没错  反过来就不成立了
Exactly. And it's not like the opposite would work.
男人童言童语地说话
There's no way a guy could pick up a girl,
是泡不到妞的
going around talking like a little boy.
-接受挑战  -不
- Challenge accepted.  - No.
我  巴尼・斯丁森
I, Barney Stinson,
能用童言童语泡到妞
will pick up a girl whilst talking like a little boy.
这是我想的名字候选单
Okay. Here's my list of baby names.
泰拉怎么样
Oh. What about "Tara"?
不  泰拉不行
No. Not "Tara."
泰拉是我们学校的校花
Tara was the hottest girl in my high school.
我们所有人都对她着迷
We were all, like, obsessed with her.
我们不仅仅谈论她
We didn't just talk about her
意淫她
and fantasize about her...
还写了一首歌  歌颂她
We wrote songs about her.
泰拉  你翘臀的曲线  迷死人 *
* Tara, your booty is so smooth
希望这不会太无礼 *
* And I hope this isn't rude
但我真的想上它 *
* But I want to get up on it.
泰拉不行
Not "Tara."
埃斯特怎么样
What about "Esther"?
先生们  先生们
Gentlemen, gentlemen.
即将登上主台的是
Coming up on the main stage,
埃斯特  掌声欢迎
give it up for Esther!
喂  巴尼
Oh. Oh. Hey, Barney.
那个肋排肉确实很不错
That prime rib was surprisingly good,
但现在才早上十点半
but it's 10:30 in the morning.
我还没性趣看女人跳脱衣舞
I don't need to see a lady get naked and dance.
衣服是肯定脱掉的
Oh, Esther gets naked.
但是埃斯特不表演跳舞
But she doesn't dance.
那她干嘛
Then what does she do?
偶滴个神呐
Sweet mother nature!
这真是我刚抽的牌
That was my card!
先生们  先生们
Gentlemen, gentlemen.
再次为埃斯特  献上热烈的掌声
Give it up for Esther!
埃斯特不行
Not "Esther."
我得来一杯  泰德  泰德
I need a drink. Ted? Ted?
马修  你的名单是全是男孩名
Marshall, your list is entirely boy names.
你知道你有大概一半的可能
You do realize there's roughly a 50% chance
会生个女儿的吧
of you having a daughter, right?
好吧  说实在的  我从没想过会生女孩
Okay, honestly, I've never thought about having a girl.
我也不想去考虑生女孩的事
I don't want to think about having a girl.
泰拉  埃斯特
Tara, Esther--
你能想象当那种妞的老爹  有多悲惨吗
can you imagine being one of those girls' dads?
马修的乖女儿*
* Marshall's daughter
你的翘臀*
* Your booty
翘臀的曲线  迷死人*
* Your booty's so smooth.
先生们  先生们
Gentlemen, gentlemen.
即将登上主台的是  热烈欢迎马修的乖女儿
On the main stage, give it up for Marshall's daughter.
是他毁了我的童年
He screwed up my childhood.
我才会堕落干这行
That's why I do this.
我完全不知道该怎么养女儿
I have no idea how to raise a daughter!
万一她走歪路  怎么办
What if she makes bad choices?
我是说  要是她最后和那些...
I mean, what if she winds up dating some...
上帝啊
Oh, God.
老爸  我要给你介绍我的新男友
Papa, I want you to meet my new boyfriend.
好啊  兄弟
Hey, bro.
感谢你生出如此尤物
Thanks for making such a hottie.
谁是爹O
Who's your daddy?
你咯  因为我们嘿咻得那么爽
You are, 'cause of all the sex we have.
我不想要女儿
I don't want a girl.
我只想要个小子
I just want a little boy.
大伙别误会  我们是正常取向
It's not what it sounds like, folks.
嗨  老妈  老爸
Hey, Mom. Hey, Dad.
马修  是你吗
Marshall? Is that you?
呃  那个
Oh, okay, um...
你们俩离摄像头太近了
You guys, you're a little too close to the camera.
能往后退退吗
Can you back up a bit?
这样行吗
How's this?
每回都这样
Every time.
你们能不能就坐在电脑前
Um, can you just sit in front of the computer
像个正常人类
like normal human beings?
很好
Perfect!
Perfect.
怎么啦  射手
What's up, shooter?
老实说  我有点害怕
Um, to be honest, I'm getting a little freaked out
要是生个女儿怎么办
about the idea of having a daughter.
我知道你们也没啥经验
I know you two probably aren't the right people to talk to about this.
你们生了一窝小子
You had all boys.
呃  那是走了狗屎运
Oh, well, that was just dumb luck.
亲爱的  你能给我从小屋里拿瓶啤酒吗
Hey, honey, would you get me a brewski from out of the shed?
当然  你要什么吗  马修
Sure. You want anything, Marshall?
我在电脑这边  妈
I'm in a computer, Mom.
是啊  都是儿子
Yeah, all boys.
完全华丽丽的巧合
Total co-winky-dink.
压根没巧合这回事
It was no co-winky-dink.
自维京时代以来
Since the Viking age,
埃里克森家族便世代相传着一个怀上男孩的
the Eriksen men have passed down ancient secrets
古老秘方
for conceiving boys.
第一  避开柠檬
Number one, avoid lemons.
那是女婴的肥料
They're baby girl fertilizer.
好吧  没别的意思  老爸
Okay... No offense, Dad,
但我强烈怀疑这没有科学依据
but I doubt there's any scientific data to support--
"我强烈怀疑这没有科学依据"
"I doubt there's any scientific data to support.."
我生的都是儿子
I had all sons.
你爷爷生的都是儿子
Your grandfather had all sons.
你曾爷爷生的都是儿子
Your great-grandfather had all sons.
事实胜于雄辩
Scoreboard!
你要听谁的
Who you gonna listen to?
你爹我  还是"科学依据"
Me? Or "Scientific data"?
八国集团领导峰会  今日在维也纳召开
Members of the G-8 convened today in Vienna
商讨关于应对气候变化的举措
to discuss plans to fight climate change by re-
干嘛
What?
问问人家昨天干什么了
Ask me what I did yesterday.
贝基  这是我们新闻播报时段  明白吗
Hey, Becky, Becky, this is our news segment, okay?
没人关心你昨天干嘛了
Nobody cares what you did yesterday.
别生气嘛  罗宾
Lighten up, Robin.
小甜心  昨天你做什么啦
What'd you do, sweetheart?
麦克
Mike!
人家刚来这里  人生地不熟
Well, I'm new in town and don't know many people.
但昨天  我遇到了个无比贴心的男人
But yesterday, I met the sweetest man,
带我游览了整个城市哦
who took me on a tour of the city.
大伙  纽约真是帅呆了
Guys, New York is kind of cool.
好了  回到八国集团领导峰会
Okay, back to the G-8 conference.
喂
Hello?
麦克  我能进镜头吗
Mike, can I get in the shot?
好极了
Fantastic.
之后  这个帅哥
Then this cutie patootie
带我去了一个叫麦凯伦酒吧
took me to this bar called MacLaren's,
就在他的公寓楼下哦
right underneath his apartment.
等下  你是跟泰德・莫斯比出去吗
Wait-- did you go out with Ted Mosby?
没错
Yes!
大伙  我和罗宾的室友一起出去哦
Guys, I went out with Robin's roommate.
我还看到她的卧室了哦
I saw her bedroom.
她可是个邋遢女王呢
She's a messy Bessie.
另一则消息  今天的晚些时候
In other news, later today,
一位曼哈顿建筑师的喉咙  将遭受一拳重击
a Manhattan architect gets punched in the throat.
泰德  纽约遍地都是妞儿
Ted, of all the women in New York,
你非得去泡一个八岁女孩吗
You had to go out with an eight-year-old girl?
大家别误会  我是正常取向
Not what it sounds like, folks.
泰德  你知道我讨厌她
Ted, you know that i hate her.
你怎么可以跟她出去约会呢
How could you go out on a date with this girl?
我们没有约会
It wasn't a date.
她来我们公寓找你
She came over to the apartment looking for you.
我做了最拿手的巧克力碎片饼干给罗宾哦
I made Robin my famous chocolate chip cookies.
但是我放的不是巧克力碎片  而是熊熊软糖
But instead of chocolate chips, I used gummie bears.
有蜘蛛
A spider!
我来猜猜  她是不是装成一个无助的小女孩
Let me guess, she acted like a helpless little girl,
而你就成了那个救了她的英勇猛男
and you stepped in as the big, strong man.
我不确定事发当时是不是那样
I don't know if that's totally true.
没事的  小宝贝
It's okay, little darlin'.
好可怜的小蜘蛛
Poor spider.
只有蜘蛛消亡了  树木才能得以成长
Spiders gotta die so trees can grow.
然后我紧紧抱住她  告诉她不会有事的
Then I held her tight and told her it was all gonna be okay.
对了  我好像只是弄伤了那只蜘蛛
By the way, I think I only wounded the spider.
它后来爬进了我卧室
It crawled off into my bedroom.
等等  你昨晚睡在沙发就是因为这事吗
Wait. Is that why you slept on the couch last night?
是啊  我一宿不敢合眼
Yeah, I slept.
快折腾死哥了
I'm dying out here.
女人们根本不吃童言童语这一招
Talking like a little boy is not working with the ladies.
哇  小姐
Wow, lady.
你的奶奶好大哇
You got some tig ol' bitties!
天啊
Gosh!
你的身体有这
Your body's a perfect...
这么完美
this many.
你好
Hi.
咱们用游泳衣遮住的部分玩摔跤  怎么样
Do you want to wrestle with our special bathing suit places?
给点力啊
Come on!
给我两秒钟就好  宝贝
I just need two seconds, baby.
我知道你可能会觉得  这是在夸奖你
I know you think that's a compliment,
但我还是希望你慢慢来
but I'd rather you took your time.
不是的  我马上回来
No, um... I'll be right back.
古代北欧的知识显示  想生儿子
Ancient Norse wisdom tells us that, to sire a son,
在你与夫人行房之前  必须先做三件事
you must do three things right before you lay with your maiden.
一  吃腌鲱鱼
First, eat pickled herring.
吃下去
Eat it!
这就是歪理谬论
This is ridiculous.
先生们  先生们  在主舞台上
Gentlemen, gentlemen, on the main stage,
为爱放弃大好前程
throwing her life away,
让我们一起为马修的乖女儿鼓掌
give it up for Marshall's daughter!
谁是你的爷爷
Who's your granddaddy?
那家伙
That guy.
你想要跟我  以及我幻想的朋友一起3P吗
Hey, want to have a three-way with me and my imaginary friend?
他的名字叫欧提斯
His name's Otis.
你想来我家一起玩传声筒电话吗
Hey, hey, want to come to my house and play telephone?
我有绳索  你有罐子
I got the string; you got the cans.
我尿裤子了
I wet myself!
你愿意帮我换衣服吗
Will you change me?
是我也会甩头走人  有点过了
Can't blame her on that one.
大伙们
Guys...
我有个很惨很惨的消息
I have some terrible, terrible news.
我  巴尼・斯丁森
I, Barney Stinson,
没办法用童言童语来泡到一个妞
can't pick up a girl whilst talking like a little boy.
挑战放弃
Challenge forfeited.
-没事  根本没人在乎  -没人向你挑战
- Yeah, we don't care about this... - No one challenged you,
所以那根本不算是个挑战
so it wasn't really a challenge.
我对不起你们
I'm sorry.
吉拉德  你那衣服是怎么回事
Hey, Gerard, what's with that shirt?
穿着那衣服  鬼才会被你泡到
Nobody could pick up a chick wearing that thing.
挑战接
Challenge accept...
我很庆幸那终于结束了
Wow, I'm glad that's over.
巴尼像个孩子般说话  真令人起鸡皮疙瘩
It was creepy watching Barney talk like a little kid.
但是贝基那样说话  你就无法抵抗吗
Oh, but you find it irresistible when Becky does?
我真搞不懂
I don't get it.
那位跟我交往过的泰德
The Ted that I went out with
居然会喜欢一个  在没人成人监管下
was attracted to the kind of woman
不能独自使用一把牛排刀的女人
who could use a steak knife without supervision.
事实上  贝基不喜欢牛排
For your information, Becky doesn't like steak,
她喜欢大意利面
she likes pasghetti.
意大利面
Spaghetti.
更重要的是  她令我感觉被人需要
And more importantly, she makes me feel needed.
被需要
Needed?
她让学步车感到被需要
She makes training wheels feel needed.
被人需要的感觉很好  而且你知道吗
Hey, it's nice to feel needed. And you know what?
那是种跟你在一起的男人  无法得到的感觉
It's not a feeling guys get when they're with you.
儿啊
Son...
维京人的学问告诉我们  想确保
Viking lore tells us that to ensure the continuation
你的高贵男性血脉得以延续
of your noble male lineage...
弄一大碗的冰块
Get a big old bowl of ice
然后把你的蛋蛋狠狠地泡进去
and dunk your man sack right in there!
你俩在聊你们的大球球呢
You two and your football.
好吧
Okay.
接下来上床准备行动  先把莉莉转向北方
Now get in there, point Lily due north
然后就给我搞个孙子出来
and make me a grandson!
埃里克森  勇往直前
Eriksen!
当年我们在约会时  我没让你感觉被需要吗
When we were dating, I... I didn't make you feel needed?
拜托  你在任何事上都想要主控权
Come on! You always took charge of everything.
交给我吧
I got this.
谢谢
Thanks.
这样还行吗  我有没弄疼你
This okay? Am I hurting y...
交给我吧
I got this.
有人想闯进来  叫警察
Someone's trying to break in-- call the cops.
交给我吧
I got this.
那很困扰你吗
Did that really bother you?
有一点吧  被人需要的感觉很好
Well, yeah. It's nice to be needed.
我很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry.
我不是故意要让你不开心的
I didn't mean to upset you.
是贝基
It's Becky.
她被困在了一个旋转门里
Aw, she's trapped in a revolving door.
交给我吧
I got this.
好
Yeah.
来搞个孩子吧
Let's make a baby!
宝贝  你那是雪球
Baby, you're packing snowballs,
而且你的口气闻起来像是一股屁味
and your breath smells like a mermaid fart.
爱死了你的浪语
Loving the dirty talk.
但你知道什么更让人情欲高涨吗
But you know what's even hotter?
头冲这边更爽哦
If we face this a way.
我们好坏坏
Ooh, we're bad.
等等  宝贝
Wait... hey, baby,
为什么你要把我转向北方
why are you facing me north?
你想让我生个儿子
You're trying to make us have a boy.
我  可以  解
I... can ex...
你怎么知道头冲北这件事
How do you know about the north thing?
还有那些柠檬是怎么回事
And what are you doing with those lemons?
女孩受孕法
Baby girl fertilizer!
你想生个女儿
You're trying to make us have a girl!
你居然想生个女儿
You are tring to make us have a girl.
我最不喜欢的学生都是男孩子
All my least favorite students have been boys.
所以我在谷歌上搜索"女孩制造大法"
So I Googled "how to make a girl"--
一堆很黄很暴力的东西出现
some really weird stuff came up
不过最后我找到了一个  受孕的网站
but finally, I found this conception web site
它说你应该
that said you should...
在行房时  面向南方
Point south at the moment of conception...
吃个柠檬
eat a lemon...
把你的私密处  慢慢加热到40度左右
and heat up your lady parts to a balmy 105 degrees.
感觉还不赖
Oh, that's not bad.
埃里克森  勇往直前
Eriksen!
莉莉  你怎么可以
Lily, how could you do...
跟我做一模一样的事情呢
exactly the same thing I did?
你本应该支持我  跟我一样想要男孩
You're supposed to be the same one.
瞧  又是个期望女人
See that? Another boy expecting a woman
来给自己过失善后的男孩
to clean up his mistakes.
这就是女孩比男孩强的原因
That's why girls are way better than boys.
是吗  那为什么每部恐怖片里
Oh, really. Well, then how come whenever there's
演那种令人毛骨悚然的小孩  都是个小女孩呢
a creepy kid in a horror movie it's always a little girl?
又或是一对女双胞胎  她们连说话都是
Or twin girls, who speak...
异口同声
in unison.
那恰奇呢[美国恐怖片《鬼娃孽种》里的主人公]
Oh, well, what about Chucky?
第一  他是个公仔
Okay, A) He was a doll;
第二  是在成人连环杀手指使他做事
B) He was possessed by an adult serial killer;
第三  你为什么要在睡前提起恰奇呢
and C) How could you bring up Chucky right before bed?
呃  我们约会的时候
Um, when we were dating,
我  我有让你感觉被需要过吗
did... did I make you feel needed?
没  我一点儿也感觉不到你需要我
No, I didn't feel like you needed me at all.
果然不出所料
That's what I thought.
-打扰了  -等等  你这是
- Uh, I'm sorry. - Wait, where are you...
这是种赞美
That's a compliment.
你是我见过最独立的女人
You are the least needy woman I've ever met
这种女人最棒了
that's awesome.
我是说  没有人敢问罗宾・施巴斯基
I mean, no guy's gonna say
"谁是你爹地"
"Who's your daddy?" to Robin Scherbatsky.
你就是自己的主人
You're your own daddy.
不但身兼母职
And mommy.
有时候还像个住在小木屋的奇怪幸存大叔
And weird survivalist uncle who lives in a cabin
边扛着猎枪  边抱怨着政府
with a shotgun blaming stuff on the government.
你是我上过最棒  最坚强
And that is what makes you the most amazing, strong...
最独立的女人
independent woman I've ever banged.
谢谢  巴尼
Thanks, Barney.
呃  有个事
You know, um...
我从刚才就一直想问你
there's something that I wanted to ask you,
但我不知道怎么开口  那我说啦
and I don't really know how to say it so... here goes.
穿着围裙那个疯婆子是谁
Who's the crazy chick in the apron?
有个小淘气把他的公仔扔地上了
Someone naughty left his toys on the floor
作为惩罚  我要打小屁屁咯
and needs to be spanked on his tushy-tush.
哇哦  我刚可是戴着套的哦
Uh-oh, I'm in "twubble."
你怎么做到的
You did it? How?
昨晚  在承认战败之后
Last night, after admitting defeat,
我放纵自己
I just let myself go.
哇  看起来很好吃的样子
Mmm, that looks so good.
可以分点给我吗
Can I have some?
不行
No!
这是我的冰淇淋  不给你吃
It's my ice cream; you can't have any.
你应该学学如何分享
Someone needs to teach you how to share.
让妈咪来教教你吧
Who's your mommy?
挑战完成
Challenge completed!
现在  你能不能把这怪胎弄走
Now, uh, can you get this freak out of here?
我好怕怕哦
I'm really scared.
交给我吧
I got this.
所以你们终于在名字上达成共识了
Oh, so you finally agreed on a name?
那是因为
Uh, well,
有天晚上  她发高烧
the other night she ran a really high fever.
凌晨三点  我们抱着她冲到急诊室
We rushed her to the emergency room at 3:00 in the morning,
但没有名字  医院不愿意接收她
But they wouldn't admit her without a name.
就在那时  我们意识到我们的行为有多么愚蠢
Right then and there, we realized how stupid we were being.
我们看着对方
We looked at each other
名字就这么脱口而出
and, well, we just knew.
我们宝宝叫
Our baby's name is...
埃斯特
Esther.
Esther?
埃斯特
Esther!
真是个好名字
That's beautiful.
对啊
Yeah.
我们真愚蠢
We're idiots.
宝贝  孩子的名字和性别
Baby, names and gender, it's just, like..
在某种程度上  给我们一种错觉
it's some way of giving ourselves the illusion
以为我们能控制任何一切
that we have any control whatsoever.
我只想要一个健康快乐  重达将近11斤
I-I just want a healthy, happy, 12-pound--
哇哦
Whoa.
那9斤
Ten-pound?
7斤
Eight-pound?
我尽力吧  但是伙计
I guess, but, dude,
你一口气说了三个  我怕我的肚子不给力啊
you're writing checks my vagina can't cash.
我爱你
I love you.
无论生出来是男是女  我都会爱死我们的宝宝
And I'm gonna love the crap out of whatever baby we have.
我也是
Me, too.
你知道吗
You know what?
咱们应该先想一个男女通用的名字
We should just think of a name that's good for either a girl or a boy.
比如
Like, um...
杰米
Jamie.
马修
Marshall...
咱们宝宝有名字了
we just named our baby.
杰米
Jamie.
杰米绝对不行
Not Jamie.
鞋带开了  我帮你系上
Shoe's untied. I got it.
对  是该适可而止了
Yeah, this is over.